

Sergio Ortega

DEVELOPER



Contact

my email: instintoimagen@gmail.com

📍 my location: Córdoba, Argentina

✓ visit my website: <u>sergioortega.com.ar</u>

connect on linkedin: <u>linkedin.com/in/sergioortegadev</u>

my GitHub repo: github.com/sergioortegadev

my tweets: twitter.com/sergioortegadev

About me

Developer with experience in layout of prototypes designed with creativity, user friendly, and following UX guidelines.

Programmer specialized in web technologies such as JavaScript, React, API consuming, and also Node, Java and MySQL. Git and Github handling. Interested in scalable projects, with agile methodologies like SCRUM and CI/CD processes.

Always a technology enthusiast, I am a born self taught, and I keep myself constantly updated.

Portfolio



See my projects

Skills function busquedaDesarrollador

- web app development
- web design and layout
- Self-taught
- effective Communication
- analytical skill
- console log "Hagamos una entre content creator for digital media, professional photographer, and teacher

Technologies and tools

Javascript

React.js

Node.js

creatividad) (

10

if (experiencia > tresAños) (I Technologia Estás Contratado!

Java

Musq MySQL

Bootstrap

HTML

CSS

Git



GitHub

Photoshop

After Effects

Linux



Wordpress

Lightroom

Premiere

Education

- Mainly self-taught 🚀
- 2023 Agile methodologies | UNC Min. Ciencia y Tecnología verification code
- 2023 Argentina Programa y Ticmas
- 2022 Argentina Programa
- 2022 Cisco NDG Linux Unhatched
- 2016 Technical in photography- UPC
- 2012 Film and television degree UNC

Experience



• Freelance Developer (2022 - present)

Web app development, landing page, and e-commerce. Designed with creativity, user friendly, following UX guidelines. Programmer specialized in web technologies such as JavaScript, React, API consuming, and also Node, Java and MySQL.



• Tv Channel 10 - SRT UNC (2015 - present)

Tv program director. (2020 - present).

Tape operator & video editor (2015 - 2020).



• **Aplitivo**.com (2021)

Developer, content creator, and SEO. Education site with e-commerce.



• **InstintoImagen**.com.ar (2003 - 2022)

Developer, designer, and SEO.

Photo and video studio.



• **La Voz** (2011 - 2013)

Hired photographer for the newspaper in the indicated period, and I also continued as a freelance photographer for the same means until 2022.



• Apex América (2007 - 2011)

Trainer (customer-certified trainer) for new entries to internet technical support telephone service. Also quality analyst and internet technical customer support.

SIEMENS • SIEMENS (2007)

Customer support.